tradingeconomics.com 2011-05-28

# Free Economic Indicators Charts, Historical Data, News and Forecasts

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Security Technology**

Trading Economics uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submit. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than Trading Economics while it is being transmitted to us. We work hard to ensure that our Web sites are secure and that they meet industry standards. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers), and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data. 

**About Cookies**

Cookies are small files containing information that a Web site uses to track its visitors. Trading Economics may set and access Trading Economics cookies on your computer, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring users to our Web site. Trading Economics or any of its divisions may use cookies in connection with Trading Economics products and services to track your activities on our Web sites. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous and not personally identifiable. 

**Sharing Information with Our Affiliates**

We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as servicing customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us as well as companies that have an ownership interest in our company. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information described above, such as your name, address, and account information. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent Trading Economics does in accordance with this Policy. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

Trading Economics does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with Trading Economics, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to Trading Economics. Non-affiliated companies that assist Trading Economics in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that Trading Economics dictates. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your expressed consent. We want you to know that Trading Economics will not sell your personal information. 

**Regulatory Disclosure**

Under limited circumstances, Trading Economics may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose, unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission. 

**Opt Out  
**   
You are not required to supply any of the personal information that we may request; however, failure to do so may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account or to provide services to you. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete, and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information.
